https://danieldefense.com/privacy-policy-disclaimers/

We use cookies to make your experience better.
To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies.
Learn more.
Privacy Policy/Disclaimers
This Website Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, and Disclaimer (collectively referred to as “Privacy Policy”) is provided by Daniel Defense, LLC (commonly referred to as “Daniel Defense,” “we,” “our,” or “us”). The Privacy Policy is applicable to our website www.danieldefense.com (commonly referred to as "Website"), and it governs data collection and your usage of our Website.  It does not apply to information we obtain or collect through means other than our Website.
PLEASE READ THIS WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND DISCLAIMERS OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AS IT MAY BE AMENDED OR MODIFIED FROM TIME TO TIME AS DESCRIBED HEREIN BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO SUCH TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND DISCLAIMERS, DO NOT ACCESS OUR WEBSITE.
Data Collection
This Privacy Policy includes a description of our policies with respect to our collection and use of certain information through our Website. We may collect two types of information from you: (a) personal information that you voluntarily provide to us, and (b) usage information concerning our Website that we automatically collect as you interact with our Website.
a) Personal Information that You Voluntarily Provide to Us
The majority of times that you visit our Website, your use can occur without you telling us who you are and without providing any information about yourself. However, there are times that we may ask you to voluntarily provide information ("Personal Information") about yourself through the Website.  Our requests for personal information will only occur to serve specific purposes, including, but not limited to, (1) your purchase of our products; (2) for you to receive our newsletters/e-blast or other marketing material; (3) for you to participate in user surveys; (4) to process your registration with our Website, including verifying that your e-mail address is active and valid; (5) to improve our Website; (6) to communicate with you regarding information such as products, services, or offers, which we believe you may be interested; (7) to respond to your inquiries; (8) to contact you regarding any of our contests, sweepstakes, or promotions within which you have participated: (9) for our own internal business purposes; and (10) for other purposes as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
We will not sell, rent, or lease your Personal Information to third parties. However, we may need to provide limited Personal Information to third parties for the purposes of processing orders, processing credit card and other payment transactions, and to deliver products or services to you that you have purchased. Personal financial information will only be used for the reason it was provided, such as to complete a purchase. You are under no obligation to provide us with Personal Information. However, your refusal to provide requested Personal Information will likely limit your ability to participate in certain services or activities offered on our Website, particularly when the requested Personal Information is noted as being mandatory or required for you to participate in a particular service or activity.
b) Cookies; Information We May Automatically Collect
We will not sell, rent, or lease your Personal Information to third parties. When you visit our website, we store cookies on your browser to collect information. The information collected might relate to you, your preferences or your device, and is mostly used to make the site work as you expect it to and to provide a more personalized web experience. However, you can choose not to allow certain types of cookies, which may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer. Click on the different category headings to find out more and change our default settings according to your preference. You cannot opt-out of our First Party Strictly Necessary Cookies as they are deployed in order to ensure the proper functioning of our website (such as prompting the cookie banner and remembering your settings, to log into your account, to redirect you when you log out, etc.). For more information about the First and Third Party Cookies used please follow this link.
Strictly Necessary Cookies
These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.
Performance Cookies
These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.
Social Media Cookies
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to the site to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit. If you do not allow these cookies you may not be able to use or see these sharing tools.
Targeting Cookies
These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store directly personal information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.
Consent to Transfer Information to the United States
All of our Website are operated in the United States and all information our Website collect will be processed and stored in databases located in the United States. Thus, if you are in a location outside of the United States, by using our Website you consent to the transfer to and processing of your information in the United States.
Our Policies Regarding Children
If you are under 18 years of age, please do not submit any information without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian. We will not knowingly collect Personal Information about any person under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at: webadmin@danieldefense.com.
Our Website Security
We will take commercially reasonable security measures to protect and secure your Personal Information. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or electronic storage of information can be 100% secure. Thus, while Daniel Defense strives to protect your Personal Information, we cannot warrant the security of any Personal Information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your Personal Information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security in our systems.
Consent to Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective seven (7) days following us posting a revised Privacy Policy on our Website. Your continued use of our Website seven (7) days following such posting means you accept and consent to those changes.
Contests, Sweepstakes, and Promotions
We may, from time to time, at our sole discretion, offer contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions (collectively referred to as "Contests") through our Website.  If you choose to participate in a Contest, Personal Information about you may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the Contest as required by applicable law or the rules that govern the Contest.  Such Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, announcement of winners and prize fulfillment.  Additionally, by participating in a Contest, you are agreeing and consenting to the official rules that govern such Contest.
Business Transfers and Corporate Changes
We reserve the right to disclose and transfer Personal Information to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of one or more of the Website, or in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, or restructuring, corporate sale, or other corporate change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.
Required Disclosures
We may disclose your personal information, without notice to you, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served on Daniel Defense; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Daniel Defense; or (3) under exigent circumstances, to protect the personal safety of users of our Website or the public.
Ownership
Daniel Defense owns all the information presented on our Website and has copyrights, trademarks and patents where applicable on such information. However, Daniel Defense may share approved third party content (i.e., Blog on DD Wire, etc.) wherein Daniel Defense will attribute the appropriate ownership and/or credit to the third party content. All opinions, ideas, suggestions, and other feedback submitted through our Website may be used by us, without any restriction and without charge, and nothing contained in this Privacy Policy shall limit or otherwise affect this.
Public Message Boards/Reviews
If you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through public message boards available through our Website, such information may be collected and used by third parties and is not subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Additionally, our Website may provide opportunities for you to post reviews of our products and services. Such reviews are not subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Further, although we are not required to monitor such reviews, we reserve the right to remove any reviews that we, in our sole discretion, find offensive, abusive, racist, sexist, homophobic, immoral, sexually explicit, or otherwise objectionable. Additionally, we may remove such reviews if they contain information personal to you or others, such as email addresses, phone numbers, names, addresses, or website addresses.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES
THE WEBSITE IS PROVIDED "AS-IS", AND DANIEL DEFENSE DISCLAIMS TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW ALL WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE WEBSITE, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITE, THE CONTENTS, INFORMATION, AND MATERIALS OF THE WEBSITE, WHETHER SUCH WARRANTIES  ARE EXPRESS, IMPLIED, OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR TITLE, WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE, OR WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OR INTERFERENCE WITH ENJOYMENT. BY WAY OF EXAMPLE, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DANIEL DEFENSE DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE WEBSITE WILL FULFILL ANY USER'S PARTICULAR REQUIREMENTS OR EXPECTATIONS, THAT ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE, OR THAT ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE IS ACCURATE.  SPECIFIC WARRANTIES OFFERED BY US ON ANY PRODUCTS SOLD ON OUR WEBSITE GOVERN OVER THE DISCLAIMERS CONTAINED IN THIS PARAGRAPH.
DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY
NEITHER DANIEL DEFENSE NOR ANY OF THEIR AFFILIATES, LICENSORS, PARTNERS, MANAGERS, SHAREHOLDERS, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, AGENTS, OR EMPLOYEES SHALL HAVE ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY TO ANY USER FOR ANY DAMAGES, WHETHER GENERAL, SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL, INCLUDING ANY LOST PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT FORESEEABLE AND WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, COMMON LAW, OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY, STATUTE, OR REGULATION. USER EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES THAT DANIEL DEFENSE IS PROVIDING ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE IN RELIANCE ON THE DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES THAT SUCH DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS ARE REASONABLE. IN NO EVENT SHALL DANIEL DEFENSE’ LIABILITY TO ANY USER EXCEED THE AMOUNTS ACTUALLY PAID BY USER FOR USE OF THE WEBSITE.
Pricing/Specifications
Prices and specifications for any products or services sold through our Website are subject to change without notice.  Typographic, photographic, and /or descriptive errors are subject to correction.  In the event that we determine, in our sole discretion, that we have made an error concerning, but not limited to, the price, specification, quantity, or description of one or more of our products or services, any sale or transfer of said products or services shall be made subject to our correction(s). All prices are quoted in US$.
We welcome your questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not followed our Privacy Policy, please contact us at webadmin@danieldefense.com.
This Privacy Policy was last updated December 7, 2020.
